Hey! Could you be quiet for a moment?
It's too noisy.
We can't rest!
It's okay. Don't cry.
Thank you, Hye Jin.
San, come here.
Good boy! Good job!
You are doing excellent.
Madam, you see how he is running.
What a little man our San is.
Does your father have vascular dementia?
Yes.
How about your husband?
You must make a full preparation for the parole hearing of next week.
Mum.
You could be released in 18 mounths.
It's your only chance to keep your child with you.
I know.
Hang on and keep from any trouble, please.
I will.
Ho! Why so sad?
Hit and Run girl, what makes you so pleased all the days?
Why not share it with us?
Giving birth to a bastard is not something decent.
Why can't you live with most carefulness here?
San, thanks to you, I'm so tired.
Are you going to keep crying tonight?
Stay away from him!
How dare you?
What? Do you want to hit me?
Right! You have your parole hearing coming up.
Go ahead and hit me. Hit me!
What a selfish bitch you are!
You are kept here because you killed someone.
Don't you feel sorry for your child?
No matter how much you care for him,
he would be condemned as the son of a murderer after he is out.
Could you stop it?
It's too much for a child.
You've got a dear friend here, except for your son.
Why don't you live here forever?
Yoo Jung, have you considered sending San away from the jail？
Huh?
You can't keep him here forever.
I gave mine up for adoption.
When I was sixteen.
I gave birth to a baby in the same jail.
I sent her away when she was 8 months old.
Don't give me that look.
That mother must be more qualified than me.
It's better for her to stay away from this jail.
But a mother should take care of her own baby.
Hye Jin, I'm sure you would be a good mother.
San has a father.
He has a father and a grandfather.
I'm not sending him anywhere.
Damn.
I'm sick of it.
You can't behave like this all the time.
I only have one day off each week.
If you come here after 9,
you need to pay me more money.
I'm sorry.
Have some food please.
No.
I won't eat until Yoo Jung comes.
You have to eat.
No!
A letter?
If you eat, I'll read it to you.
Read it first.
Dad. Do Hoon.
Dad, have you had meals regularly? Have you taken medicine in time?
Try not to give the nurse a hard time, please.
I'm a picky eater as you,
but the food here is really good.
You might find me round when I return.
Every day I'm learning something new.
So everyday is new and fun.
Dad, please exercise regularly and keep fit.
I'm working well with my roommates.
Don't worry about me. Please take good care of yourself.
Oops! Yoo Jung, you dropped something.
No. 2014, what are you doing?
It's a diaper. Do you want me to have it?
But it's too small for me.
His diaper.
Please take good care of it.
Do Hoon, San is a big boy now.
He was jogging around yesterday.
We have taken a photo.
I hope all three of us can take a picture together. I can't wait to run into that day.
I love you.
Please take good care of my dad.
I'll write again.
We can eat at a restaurant there.
Don't be silly. Why waste money?
That's why we still live in poverty.
It's too expensive to eat at the airport.
Why are you so late?
I thought you parted with that girl very early.
You didn't go to Yoo Jung's, did you?
The nurse is taking care of him. Why you have to be there.
Please buy something good with it.
It's been a while since you went on a trip.
It's okay. We don't need money.
Your salary isn't high enough.
Just forget about Yoo Jung.
We've done enough.
We took care of her father at the hospital,
and gave money to the victim's family.
Yoo Jung has little to say about us.
Please stop it! Yoo Jung didn't mean to hit someone.
I don't care. I just won't let you marry someone with a criminal record.
You're a prosecutor and she's murderer.
No way.
I'd made it clear.
I feel bad for Yoo Jung's father.
Some day ago, he said would join me on the trip to Jeju Island this autumn.
Why am I always the bad person?
Do you think I'm enjoying this?
Do Hoon, listen to me carefully.
Don't trap yourself by love or anything elae.
Both of you would be painful by the end.
Trust me this time.
Are you leaving?
You told me your flight would be depart at 8:30.
Your father can't walk fast. We could wait at the airport.
We haven't taken plane before. I don't want any trouble of missing our flight.
What are you waiting for? Come on.
Okay.
See you later.
Listen to me, Yoo Jung.
I was poked a lot by the stuff hidden on my chest.
Some bumps appear.
You owe me a box of coffee.
I know.
It turns out that everybody is rich, except me.
You would buy this and that.
I'm the only poor one.
So you see, people must find a good God.
I mean a good mum.
Before was born to the world,
you should be in the right womb.
Look at him. He's dumping his girl.
Don't be fooled by guys like him.
I was fooled many times.
Yoo Jung, do you know why she's here?
She sold fake drugs.
She even fed her own child with sleeping pills,
so that she could do night works.
She's a complete lunatic.
They'd bring boxes of beer at night.
A lot of beers.
-46 -46
It'll be done by tomorrow.
I'll get it ready before the ceremony, master.
Congressman Shin would celebrate his 4th term on office tonight, at our hotel.
Everybody's been telling me that all the day.
Please make another set for me.
What are you doing here?
What kind of thing could it be? I'm here to see you.
I'm tired of your lies.
Did you ever come to me without a purpose?
What are you busy with?
Whenever my father has a ceremony,
he wants to show off his well-dressed daughter.
I've to get dressed and leave. Tell me your what you what.
I thought your father hoped us to get married soon,
but it's not the case.
You've changed.
You weren't interested in this matter at all.
I haven't changed.
I'm just learning to live as my father's son.
Don't worry. He's having the ceremony at your hotel.
That means he hopes us to be together still.
I have to go.
Are you still doing this?
It's my father's main project.
What?
I want to participate as well.
It seems you are a good man, prosecutor.
You can't smoke here.
I think smokers' rights are completely ignored.
Don't you agree?
Ms. Park, you are not here for fun.
The alcohol concentration in your blood is 1.13.
8 cars are hit by you.
2 stores are damaged by you.
You could've killed someone.
Good to see you again, Prosecutor Ahn.
The victims all agreed to cut a deal with us.
None of them want to press charges against her.
These are papers signed by them.
Mr. Kim.
Thank you for everything. Prosecutor Ahn.
We can go now. Miss.
We'll leave you with your work.
Don't you move? Let me in.
Where is Ahn Do Hoon?
I said move!
I don't owe anything to this country.
Very well. Let me enjoy the free food in jail. Move!
Mr. Kim Sang Bum, you are intoxicated for your interview?
So, put me in jail please.
The life is boring. I'm tired of it.
Put me in jail right away, please.
Let me go! Come on!
Do Hoon, don't forget tonight's date.
I've done a lot of work to settle it for you.
My father was a technician.
Yet he has been out of work for a while.
My mother raised me up by working as a casual labor.
You became a prosecutor in that family.
Your parents must be proud.
Yes, I'm their only hope.
I've to look after them after get married.
Since my pre-marrige time is short if I marry you,
I prefer to live apart from your parents.
I guess we are not fit for each other.
Since you wasted my time, you don't mind paying for my coffee, right?
Is that a blind date?
Hi.
She dumped you, right?
This place is filled with girls like her at this time each day.
She doesn't deserve a prosecutor.
Forget about her.
I'm fine.
I thought you are uninterested in girls.
Maybe I was wrong.
Shall I set you up with someone?
Shina Foundation
Umm.
I saw you several times in free service.
You didn't recognize me.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
You were always alone and not interested in media
Your sincerity makes you look cool.
See you next time.
Thank you for coming.
Congratulations!
Water! Give me some water!
Ok.
Shin Sang Ho, that bastard!
How dare he treat us like this? Is K Hotel some little inn?
Thanks to his rich parents he holds the position.
Can't he be modest?
How much we spend?
All the expense on grand ballroom rent, food and personnel reception added,
is about 200 million and 3 thousand KRW.
Put it under his name.
I'll collect it whatever it takes.
Yet keep in silence in front of him.
That's why he's escalating his exploitation on us.
Min Hyuk.
You've been putting your marriage off for so long.
You think it's a trade? Are you waiting for any appreciation in value?
It's a trade.
My marriage services for our merger and acquisition. I thought everybody knew it.
You're right.
Regard it as your first business deal.
Get Se Yeon, no matter what.
You prepare for Min Hyuk's inauguration.
Ok.
Congressmen Kim Chang Suk must be invited to the inauguration.
He won over Congressman Shin in this general election.
Congressman Shin won't be happy.
That's why I'm inviting him.
I guess Min Hyuk knows what I'm up to.
Parole hearing candidate...
Are you eager to regain your freedom with your bloody hands?
It's not the rule.
-Here you go. -Here you go. -Here you go. -Here you go.
San, say thank you to prosecutor. Say it.
Try to say it.
Thank you, sir. Are you married?
Move on, old lady.
Move! Give me full spoons of meat.
Here you go.
Give me more than her.
More than her.
Ok. Ok.
Anyone need more, let me know.
Water. Water. Water.
- I'll get it - OK. Good.
Crazy bitch! You're head over heels at the sight of man.
Think about your son.
Just sit down. Eat your noodles with soybean paste.
Mommy! Mommy!
Are you here just for a tour?
Then why did you want to come?
It's not my style to be a chameleon in public.
They squeeze time to do free service here.
You have no right to judge them while standing here doing nothing.
Now I'll take care of my service as well.
If K Hotel is willing to do that,
our reeducation targets would be denefit from it.
Most companies won't hire them due to prejudice.
Unprejudiced project is good for the image of my company.
It's a win-win strategy.
Industries would be provided with qualified labors.
K Hotel would be provided with necessary supplies.
Our improved image would boost sellings too.
But, sir,
there's one condition.
Excuse me?
What is this? Don't you like it, San?
How wonderful if daddy could be here again next week, right?
Do you think you would have jajangmyeon next month?
Ready for inspection!
No. 2008,
you're in possession of this banned item. As a punishment, your bonus of next month would be slashed.
I told you to be careful before your parole hearing.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not experienced enough to be a parole officer. Why would I...
That's what I'm wondering about.
Excuse me?
If it's such a surprise to you,
why don't you talk to the person who recommended you as a parole officer?
What a tough task.
Arrest them and release them. What a drama!
I've become a better actor than a prosecutor.
That future chairman asked me to pass you this.
Since when you've become so close?
Prosecutor Ahn, you look serious all the time, but you are really good at finding backers.
Icecream. I just can't stop eating it even if I'm full.
Even if I know I would have diarrhea.
That new painting in the lobby looks great.
Thanks. My father is busy with an important meeting so...
I understand your father's busy works. Don't worry.
On my! Congressman Kim.
Thank you for coming!
I must be here.
Let's go inside.
Take care.
I'm glad to introduce the new chairman of K Hotel, Jo Min Hyuk. Welcome.
Action time now.
Let's go.
Before I begin my speech,
I want to share with you a great news.
I'd like to introduce to you my partner. We'll run the hotel together.
The Couple of the Century.
-Look over here. -Over here!
What are you doing? Why didn't you tell me earlier?
It was my father's idea.
It's a warning. Don't mess with K Corporation.
For the K Corporation and our new chairman, Jo Min Hyuk.
Cheers!
Kim Chang Suk! You're under arrest for power abuse and corruption.
Corruption? What are you talking about?
What's going on?
He's such an actor!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you just treating me as a fool?
Let me get this straight. It's not between you and me, but between our fathers.
We both are treated as fools.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
Please hold on.
It's Congressman Shin.
Hello, I heard you're busy. Why are you calling me right now?
That's okay.
Our reporters will write good papers about Min Hyuk's inauguration ceremony.
You don't have to thank me.
I'll try to make time next week.
Ok.
I guess he's learned how to work with me.
If we lost Congressman Kim, we'll lost the construction project.
All of us would die if we stay with the sunken ship.
Find someone reliable to replace him.
We need to get rid of him completely.
Are you okay?
Are you feeling manipulated?
How long would Congressman Kim be kept for?
Now that he's been placed under arrest, the procuratorate won't release him easily.
Do you think so?
It's already been broadcasted. They can't ignore the public opinion.
Public opinion?
Don't take that seriously.
Only if three guys give the same remarks, the rest would trust them.
It's never a big deal for them to find that three guys.
I asked you if you were okay.
Would you comfort me if I'm not.
Have you confirm that
the illegally paid commission turns to be slush funds?
Evidence shows that the oversea corporates...
The procuratorate is trying to connect it with Congressman Kim's attempt at tax evasion.
We, the procuratorate,
show zero tolerance to corruption, power abuse and bribe taking.
We promise to take a neutral position in this investigation.
Prosecutor Ahn,
you mustn't replace lunch with icecream.
Help! Help!
Director
What's going on?
How do you feel?
Are you okay?
Are you trying to get yourself in trouble?
I thought they were your friends.
Friends, yeah right.
Stop being a goody. You make me sick.
Nice to meet you. Prosecutor Ahn.
I don't like being summoned casually by you, especially when no reason is given.
How do you do recently?
The judge decided he is of no guilt.
Don't you feel out of luck?
You were the best at the Judicial Research and Training Center. Now you just can't go well.
It's no fun, is it?
Your parents are so proud of you when you become a prosecutor.
You should be ashamed.
Because you haven't changed anything as a prosecutor.
They must have realised it as well.
It's none of your business.
I feel bad for you.
Do you think your parents would be happy
when they find out what their precious son is doing?
-What do you think? -Look!
Take this, then she would never leave the jail.
I would recommend you to your boss if you do as I tell you.
What do you want from me?
Yoo Jung, do your best.
-Try to earn an abatement from penalty. -I wil.
Please do get out of here. Stop your useless tears.
-Cheongju Correctional Institute, No. 2008! -Yes.
Kang Yoo Jung! Kang Yoo Jung!
Have a seat!
- Why are you crying? - Sorry.
I am just so sorry for those dead ones.
Sorry.
Kang Yoo Jung.
How do you spend the past 2 years?
I've been working hard to make amends for my mistake.
I've been making full use of everyday.
I believe that's what I should do.
-Do you have a son? -Yes.
Is there anyone who can take care of him?
Not really. My dad is really ill at the moment.
What are you going to do if we grant you the parole?
I heard that the girl hit by me has a mother
who is still alive.
I'm going to find her and beg for her forgiveness.
My father brought me up all by himself.
Yet when he is ill,
I can't stay with him and look after him.
So if I can get out I will spend some time with my dad.
I want to sit under stars as well.
When I'm in jail I can't be in the open air all the time.
And my son has never seen the real stars.
I want to show the stars to my son.
Thank you, Ms. Kang. You can go.
What do you want from me?
I heard that there's a parole hearing.
You're a judge of it.
What I want is quite simple.
But what do you what? To be a boss or to be a follower?
It's up to you.
Kang Yoo Jung has been punished.
Why are you still bullying her?
I can't bear her happiness, when others live in misery for her.
Would you drag your heels
due to the lack of sufficient evidence,
if Mr. Yun from Pyeongchang Construction refuse to be a testifier?
Did you hear that
Congressman Kim referred the arrest warrant as a Training Institute paper?
Are you playing a drama or broadcasting the news?
I guess Congressman Kim won't mind going to a Training Institute
to become a better citizen.
We'll make hime graduate
before he's too tired to stand on his feet.
Are you smiling at the news?
Are you crazy? She must be crazy.
Yoo Jung, are you getting out of here?
Why are you so happy?
I'm happy,
because I found that I had made a right choice. I'm so glad.
Hye Jin, I'll live with all my strength.
I'll be a good mother for San.
I'm sure.
-No. 2008. You have a visitor. -Me?
No. 2008. You have a visitor.
Who could it be?
- Is he San's father? - What? It can't be.
What do you mean? Who else would come?
That seems a young man.
Yoo Jung, wait!
Yoo Jung, put this on.
Pretty.
San, mum is going to see your father. Are you happy?
Hye Jin, take care of San please.
Nice to meet you again.
Why are you here?
Hello? Hello?
You seem to be doing okay.
You look good.
Just stay in the jail and enjoy the life inside.
Once you get out, you would find your life a real misery.
What are you doing here?
Why are you always against me？
What do you want from me?
Who are you on earth?
You must be curious why why why...
Take your time to think about why am I so hard on you.
Anyway, you won't get out this time.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
What's wrong with my cute boy? Did you poop?
It's okay. It's okay.
No. 2008. Step back.
-Take him. -San. I didn't beat him.
San. San. Let me go.
Madam! Madam! It's not me. What's wrong?
No. 2008. You can't come with him. Please go by the rule.
He was okay in the morning. I didn't do anything.
I didn't see...
Everybody! Keep working!
Madam, where are you taking San? Madam?
What's going on?
Hye Jin, what happened to San?
You're weird. Why are you asking me?
You always come to me when you need me.
- Now you blame me when something is wrong? - Hye Jin!
I'm not his mother. You are.
What are you doing?
- Let me go! - Stop! Please stop!
- You bitch! - Stop!
Why did you do that? Answer me!
I just want to save my life.
- Put it down! - Let me go! - What are you doing?
Stop! That's enough! Stop!
You are good for nothing.
Don't!
Doctor, what happened to my San? Nobody is telling me why.
- No. 2008. Stay still! - What is happening?
Why don't you tell me anything?
Where is my son? Where is San?
Where is he? Where do you take him?
Doctor, Where is my son?
Doctor! Doctor! Doctor!
Where is he? Where is he?
Where is San?
Doctor, where is my San?
Where the hell is my son? Please tell me.
I'm sorry. I'll apologize to anyone.
I can't treat her here.
Kwang Soo!
Yes.
Do you believe in love?
I think I do.
Really?
I'll tell you something interesting.
5 judges are in charge of Kang Yoo Jung's parole hearing. I met them all.
Two vote pro and two vote con.
That was what I expected. 2:2.
I'm wondering about his choice.
Love?
That's a holy shit.
Now I'm reporting investigations upon Congressman Kim,
his secret funds and other related reports.
As you see in the documents,
he obtained the government's supporting appropriate through the an account.
Since the August of 2005,
he's been served as an adjunct director of Joeun Savings Bank.
During the period, 15 billion secret funds was...
Ahn Do Hoon here.
Prosecutor.
Yoo Jung!
Ms. Kang, are you okay?
About my parole hearing...
I see. There will be a legal consulting service for you next week...
No, I don't care that.
I don't care about myself.
I could stay here for the rest of my life,
if you could get my son back.
My son...
They accuse me of child abuse.
But it's not true. You know that.
They hide San from me.
I beg you to bring back my San. Please.
What happened? Tell me in details.
They said San ate something wrong.
I don't know what's it indeed. He's bruised all over his body.
But I don't understand.
I know every inch of his body.
There isn't even a single scratch. But...
But... they said I did it.
No. He's my child...
I'm his mother.
How could I do that? Why would I hurt my son?
Calm down and listen to me.
I'll find out what happened.
Be patient and wait for my call.
Do you understand?
I'll find out what happened.
Please. Please....
Do Hoon.
They took our son.
Do Hoon! Do Hoon!
Do Hoon!
No. 2008. Time's up.
No. 2008!
Get out!
-Get out! -Let me go.
You get out! Out!
Don't touch me!
Keep away from me!
Let me go! Let me go!
Prosecutor Ahn, are you okay?
What should we do with it?
What?
Jesus.
Madam, why are you taking San's stuff?
Yoo Jung made it.
Well...
You're here. I was waiting for you all the time.
We need to finish our talk.
We've nothing to talk anout.
And, goodbye forever.
I'm transferring to the vocational training center.
I'm learning some vocational skills before my parole.
What is it?
Take it. I appreciate you a lot.
You don't have to.
Time could change everything.
Last two years past like one single moment.
I hope she could be released as soon as possible.
By then I would make her the most miserable woman in the world.
In fact, occasionally I feel it's no bad to trap her in that jail forever.
Who else would listen to those nonsense? It's nice to have you sit here.
Prosecutor Ahn, you're like my friend.
Not to mention that you always do what I wanna do.
Let's be friends.
Friendship is a mutual thing. We don't have such things.
Then, what's your opinion?
Yoo Jung!
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung.
What are you going to do if you are released?
To sit under stars.
When I was in the sport field, I realised that my son hasn't seen any real star since born.
I want show him real stars.
Next on Secret Love...
Do Hoon, we have to find San.
I've forgiven her. Now I'm relaxed.
Who is he?
He is a prosecutor named Ahn Do Hoon.
Mr. Jo Min Hyuk, there is a search warrant against you.
Let's go, dad.
I know you are the murder. You make Yoo Jung a scapgoat.
You just wait and see.